A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
Library of Virginia
- Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981). (Box 1-35.)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Galbreath, Mark A.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Giarratano, Joseph), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Gilbert, Jimmy), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Gilbert, Thomas), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Goad, Carson W.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Goad, Ernest W.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Goodwin, June A.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Graves, Theodore W., Jr.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Gray, James T.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hackett, Frank), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hammar, Harry R. III.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Harris, Richard T.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Harris, Thomas E.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Harris, William G.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Harrison, Randy), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hatch, Robinson), 1979-1981. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Heard, Emanuel F., Jr.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Herndon, William E.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hitner, Kenneth W.), 1978-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hodges, Arthur), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hogan, David L.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Hohman, Thomas F.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jackson, Rudolf), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jacobs, James), 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jacobson, William G.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (James, Franklin D.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jansen, William C.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Johnson, James M.), 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Johnson, Ralph), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Johnson, William A.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Joiner, Bruce K.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jones, David), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Jones, Jerome), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Kendrick, Hilbard), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (King, Emmitt G., III), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (King, Wister, Jr.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Knox, Richard W.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lambert, Mary M.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lane, Joyce), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lawhorne, Ronald L.), 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lawson, Elsie), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lightfoot, Geraldine), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lisenby, Larry R.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lloyd, David B.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lowery, Dean), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Lucas, Donnie A.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Magee, Joseph E.), 1976-1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Martin, James W.), 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Mathis, Cager), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Mayhew, Richard L.), 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (McBride, Douglas M.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (McKnight, J.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Moore, Robert B., Jr.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Moore, Robert E., Jr.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Morgan, Kerry), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Morris, Ernest, Jr.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Neenan, John J.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Nicholson, James C.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Nickens, Robert R.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Ossea, Edward, Jr.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Oxendine, Craig M.), 1978-1981. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Panacy, Jeffrey T.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Parks, Charles R.), 1978-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Patterson, Robert E.), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Phelps, Cecil L.), 1976. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Pollard, Abraham N.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Price, Anthony), 1977-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Proudfoot, E.E., Jr.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Pruitt, C.C.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Putnam, Allen D., Jr.), 1976-1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Queen, James), 1977-1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Richardson, Leonard E.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Robinson, David), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Robinson, James), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Roudabush, James L., Jr.), 1979-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Russell, Randolph P.), 1978-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Sanders, Mark J.), 1976. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Scott, Wendell, Jr.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Scurry, Woodrow T.), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Shah, Abdul M.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Smith, Michael M.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Smith, Nathan C.), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Soloman, Lawrence), 1976. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Stancell, John H.), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Stogsdill, Ralph, Jr.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Stokes, Edward), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Stone, Morris), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Straus, Leona), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Studds, Wayne), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Subica, Arthur), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Taylor, Fletcher), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Taylor, James S.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Thacker, Junior G.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Thomas, Teddy), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Thompson, Ida Mae), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Todd, John Lee), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Tucker, Henry), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Tyler, Walter), 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Vencil, James), undated. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Walker, George L.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Wallace, Franklin R.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Walton, Charles), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Waye, Alton), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Wesby, Luke), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Westbrook, Shiela), 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (White, Wayne), 1981. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Wilder, Erleen L.), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Williams, George A.), 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Williams, Haywood, Jr.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Winchester, K.), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Winston, Larry D.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Woodhall, Tim), 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Wyatt, Milas), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Young, Paul E., Jr.), 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Zarif, Hasan K.), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates Prisoner's Union, 1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inspection of Medical Facilities, 1977-1978. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Intensive Treatment Learning Centers (General), 1976. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Internal Investigations, 1977-1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Jails, 1978-1979. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Jails and Bed Space, 1979. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Juvenile Code, 1978. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Kennedy v. Commonwealth, 1976. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Learning Centers for Juveniles (General), 1976-1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Local Jails, 1976-1978. (Box 10)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Local Jails (Weekly Report), 1976-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) Study of Classification and Records Section, 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Mandatory Parole, 1979-1980. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Mandatory Release, 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Mandatory Release Violators, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Master Plan, 1977-1978. (Box 5)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Master Plan, 1977-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Master Plan Review, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Meal Charges, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Medical Facilities, 1976-1978. (Box 10)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Medium Security Institutions (Augusta, Buckingham, Brunswick Counties), 1976-1980. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Medium Security Institutions (Mecklenburg Correctional Center), 1976-1979. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Medium Security Institutions (Nottoway County), 1978-1981. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Medium Security Institutions (Powhatan #1, Cancelled), 1976-1979. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Mental Health Bed Space Survey, 1979-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Mental Health Facilities (Surplus), 1979. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Minority Hiring, 1976-1978. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Misdemeanants and Recidivists, 1978-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: National Survey of Good Time Laws and Administrative Procedures, 1976. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Natural Bridge Learning Center, 1977-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Newsletters, 1977-1981. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Ombudsman Services Unit, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Operation of Juvenile Detention Programs, 1978. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Overtime Study, 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Parole Process, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Peace and Social Concerns Committee (Richmond Friends Meeting), 1977. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Per Diem Pay Rates (Inmates), 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Perimeter Security Systems (Electronic), 1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Personnel Standardization Committee, 1978. (Box 10)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Pinecrest Learning Center, 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Planning Data Task Force, 1976. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Population in Local Jails, 1978-1979. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Powhatan Correctional Center, 1976-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Presentation to Appropriations Committee, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Prince William County Group Home [empty folder], 1981. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Prince William County Jail, 1978. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Prince William County Juvenile Detention Home, 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Probation and Parole, 1976-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Probation and Parole (Office at Emporia), 1979. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Proctor, Carroll, 1976-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Projected Non-General Fund Revenues, 1978-1981. (Box 9)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Properties, 1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Pulaski County Group Home, 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Purchase Requisition Regulations, 1977-1978. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Purchasing Agreement with DPS, 1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Reception and Diagnostic Center, 1977-1978. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Reference, 1978. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Regional Plan, 1978. (Box 5)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Regional Plan 1978. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Relocation Expenses, 1979-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Reorganization [2 folders], 1978-1979. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Richmond City Jail/Police Lock-Up, 1978-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Roanoke Group Home (Discovery House), 1978-1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Salary Increases, 1978. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Salary Regrade, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Salary Regrade/2.5 % Reduction, 1976-1977. (Box 6)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Sentence Reductions (Monthly), 1978-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Six-Year Expenditure Forms 1976. (Box 6)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Space Needs, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Space Utilization Standards, 1978. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Speeding Convictions and Complaints (Staff), 1979-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Standards and Agency Regulations, 1980-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Standards for Emergency Shelter Care, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Standards for Family Group Homes, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Standards for Secure Detention, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: St. Brides Correctional Center, 1976-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Study by MASD, 1976-1977. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Subpoena, 1980. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: "Take Custody and Place," 1978. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Tidewater Detention Center, 1978. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Training Academy (Waynesboro), 1978-1980. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Vacancies, 1977-1979. (Box 25)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Volunteers Involvement, 1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Work Release Program, 1976-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Youth Prison Program, 1978-1979. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Youth Services, Div. of (Educational Funds for Handicapped), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Youth Services, Div. of (Relocation of Community Group Home, Ladies Mile Manor), 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections Facilities: Medium Security Sites, 1976-1981. (Box 12)
  - Corrections Facilities: Wastewater, 1977-1980. (Box 8)
  - Corrections Planning Data Task Force, 1976-1977. (Box 30)
  - Courts: Info on Districts, Judges, Clerks, etc., 1978. (Box 3)
  - Courts: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979. (Box 3)
  - Crime Against the Elderly in the United States, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Crime Commission, 1972-1980. (Box 15)
  - Crime Commission [4 folders], 1976-1979. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Criminal Sexual Assault Task Force (SB 291), 1978-1979. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Division of Investigation, 1979-1980. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Sanger Powers Report, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Report, Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia, 1977. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Report, Children and Youth in Trouble in Virginia Phase II, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Study, Children and Youth in Trouble, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Crime Commission: Study II, Children and Youth in Trouble, 1978-1979. (Box 14)
  - Crime Control Act of 1976, 1976. (Box 4)
  - Crime Prevention Resource Directory, 1981. (Box 22)
  - Criminal Justice, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Criminal Justice: Criminal History System, 1973-1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice: Privacy and Security (Information Control and Protection of Privacy Act Of 1975), 1975-1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on, [2 folders], 1977-1980. (Box 26)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on: Appeal to Governor, City of Harrisonburg ("Listening Ear"), 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on: Appeal to Governor, Henrico County (79-A4728), 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on: Appeal to Governor, King George County (79-A4786E), 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on: Appeal to Governor, Virginia State Bar (79-A4865), 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Council on: General Correspondence, 1980. (Box 15)
  - Criminal Justice/Crime Control Issues Survey: Governor Hunt of North Carolina, 1978-1979. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Information Network (VCIN), 1973-1975. (Box 26)
  - Criminal Justice Information System, 1976-1979. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Background, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: General, 1972-1975. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: General Correspondence, 1975-1978. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: General Correspondence, 1980-1982. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Grant Progress Reports, 1976-1977. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Needs Assessment, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Offender Based State Corrections Information System (AMPS Reports), 1976-1977. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Offender Based State Corrections Information System (General), 1976-1978. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Offender Based State Corrections Information System (National Project), 1975-1977. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Offender Based Transaction Statistics, 1975-1977. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Roanoke, 1981. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Information System: Uniform Offense Codes, 1975. (Box 6)
  - Criminal Justice Management Review Board for VCIN, 1976-1981. (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice Manpower Needs Report to Secretary of Public Safety, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Criminal Justice Officers Training and Standards Commission, 1973-1979. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Planning Districts: Reorganization of, 1976-1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Priorities Plan (1981), 1979. (Box 15)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: Appointments, 1979-1980. (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: Council on Criminal Justice Subcommittees, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: General [2 folders], 1976-1978. (Box 22)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: Implementation of Criminal Justice and Personnel Information System, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: Privacy Legislation, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission: Rules and Regulations, 1981. (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice, Task Force on: Goals and Objectives, 1977. (Box 4)
  - D.P. Manager Conference, 1976-1978. (Box 32)
  - Data Processing, 1977-1978. (Box 30)
  - Data Processing: 3800 Study, 1978. (Box 30)
  - Data Processing: Personnel Classifications, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Data Processing: Program Budgeting System (PROBUD), 1979-1981. (Box 6)
  - Database Administration Task Force, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Deaf: Council and General, 1978-1980. (Box 3)
  - E.E.O. Recommendations (Mr. Heishman), 1977. (Box 32)
  - Employee Position Reports, 1977-1979. (Box 30)
  - Employee Position Reports: Study Concerning, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Engineers, Corps of, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Enterprises: Book Bindery (Corrections), 1977. (Box 8)
  - Enterprises: Laundry Facility (Powahatan Correctional Facility), 1977-1978. (Box 8)
  - Enterprises: License Plates, 1977-1979. (Box 8)
  - Environmental Impact Statement Program, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Established Positions, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Expenditure Reduction Impact Form 98-T, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Family Life, Commission on, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Family-Oriented Group Homes: York County, 1976. (Box 33)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1977. (Box 3)
  - Federal Crime Insurance Program [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Federal Department of Transportation, 1976-1978. (Box 3)
  - Federal Funds Coming to Virginia, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - Federal Law Enforcement Roles and Responsibilities Review, 1977. (Box 3)
  - Federal Legislative Tracking System Provided by IGA, 1980. (Box 2)
  - Federal Regional Council [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Federal Register, 1976-1977. (Box 2)
  - Fine Creek Correctional Center: Trailer Annex to Powhatan, 1977-1978. (Box 8)
  - Fire Detection and Security System, 1977-1981. (Box 2)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities, 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Appalachian Learning Center) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Augusta Correctional Unit #10), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Barrett Learning Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Baskerville Correctional Unit #4), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Beaumont Learning Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Bland Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Bon Air Learning Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Bon Air Reception and Diagnostic Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Botetourt Correctional Unit #25), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Buchanan Correctioanl Unit #29)[empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Capron Correctional Unit #20) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Caroline Correctional Unit #2), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Chatham Correctional Unit #15), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Chesterfield Correctional Unit), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Culpeper Correctinal Unit #11), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Deep Meadow Correctional Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Deerfield Correctional Center) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Dinwiddie Correctional Unit #27), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Fairfax Correctional Unit #30), 1978. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Floyd Correctional Unit #5) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Fluvanna Correctional Unit #12), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Halifax Correctioanl Unit #23), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Hanover Learning Center), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Harrisonburg Correctional Unit #8), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Fire Safety Inspection Reports: Corrections Facilities (Haymarket Correctional Unit #26) [empty folder], undated. (Box 3)